Chittaranjan G Nivargi

Phone: 955 257 1721

Email: chitnivargi@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

Exceedingly thorough Process Analyst with 15 years modifying ongoing business processes to achieve superlative results.

Skilled at designing and applying process changes to improve efficiency and reduce costs, without detrimentally impacting ongoing operations. Documented provider of enhancements that improve both output and worker satisfaction

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

- SAP Order Management
- Cross functional knowledge with Manufacturing, Planning, Projects and Services
- Excellent project management experience Lead
- the vendor management during the site deployments
- Proficient with of business cases

CERTIFICATION & VOLUNTEER WORK

Volunteer - Honeywell CSR Program 2010 to Present

- Collaborated with Agastya Foundation for underprivileged children education - Volunteer work Tree Plantation
- Volunteer work on child safety program
- Volunteer work on science fair for children

SAP Sales and Distribution Certified

WORK HISTORY

Lead Consultant

Bosch Global Software Technologies

September 2023 till present

- Implemented agile methodologies to successfully deliver multiple S4 HANA projects on time and within budget.
- Led and mentored a team of junior developers to improve overall project efficiency and quality.
- Improved business requirement gathering process considerably to reduce the time and improve accuracy of process.

Business Process Architect Honeywell International Ind Pvt Ltd, Pune

Jan 2013 to September 2023

- Designed, developed and implemented the concept of Warm Start.
- This considerably fastens the deployment life cycle by identifying the existing business process on a new site, understanding the gaps and transfer the legacy business to global design model. Designed new processes to meet the business requirement, which includes the integration with various modules like manufacturing, planning, projects and services.
- Excellent understanding with scenarios in product business as well as project & services business, through design and implementation experience

Order Management Consultant Honeywell International Ind Pvt Ltd, Pune Sep 2010 to Dec 2012

- Key achievement of this tenure is to deliver \$1.2 billion project which has key order management work area.
- This also has major connections with projects and services module.
- Received award for outstanding work for this project.
- Worked on designing and implementing the Order Management Forms Council process to streamline the output forms process and its enhancement cycle.

WORK HISTORY

Senior Software Engineer Wipro Technologies, Pune

Jan 2010 to Sep 2010

- Key achievement of this tenure was to understand the business process of one Europe based leading alcoholic beverage company and stabilize the project
- Task was to understand the customer business process, gather the requirement by understanding the gaps. Then design the solution, with key process underlined and show a proof of concept to customer..

Sales and Distribution Consultant Cappemini, Mumbai

Mar 2007 to Jan 2010

-Worked on an multinational pharmaceuticals company based in Chicago, USA.

Sales and Distribution Consultant Yash Technologies, Hyderabad

Worked on support project for American electronics company.

DOMAIN EXPERIANCE

Gates Unitta India Mar 2004 to Nov 2005

- -Worked as Sales and Application Engineer on this multinational non tyre rubber company.
- Closed accounts like Atlas Copco, Greaves Cotton and Bajaj Auto for industrial and automotive belts.

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS

- As Warm start leader bought down the deployment cycle by almost 12 to 16 weeks by identifying the areas which can be sorted out faster and earlier - Bought up business transformation for the site with minimum changes to business process, but by giving a business solution.
- Designed and deployed scalable processes to bring users and IT team together and execute the tasks much faster and in cyclical manner.
 Designed processes that can be rolled back on older sites at the same time can meet requirements of new sites
- Worked in different environment, culture and region, from North America to Australia.
- Received multiple awards including Bravo Platinum

EXTRA CURRICULERS

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Masters Of Management Studies Bharti Vidyapith, Pune Major in Marketing 2005-2006